<CD-RAT><Entry><HWD>LF/PRES2</HWD><Activity><GapFillInput layer="1" h="460" w="670" y="10" x="10" show-wordpool="1" wordpool-position="above"><Title alignment="left" isOn="1">Obligation and permission in the past<br /></Title><Instruction alignment="left" isOn="1">Type a phrase from the pool into the correct space.<br /></Instruction><ReferenceObject soundIsOn="0" videoIsOn="0" defaultHeight="105" alignment="left" isOn="0" /><ScrollableAssets><Asset file="04112401.jpg" folder="images/" h="151" w="170" y="9" x="477" layer="1" type="graphic" /></ScrollableAssets><Content><Question><B>Odd Jobs</B><br />‘When she was in her early twenties, my girlfriend, Lucy, used to design <br />chocolates. She loved her job because she <Gap><Score num="1" />was allowed to have</Gap> as <br />many chocolates as she wanted. Unfortunately, she <Gap><Score num="1" />couldn&apos;t bring</Gap><br />any home. She says nowadays chocolates make her feel sick.’ <I>Ben</I> <LineBreak size="13" /><br />‘In 1999 I worked as a full-time Queen Elizabeth I actor in a museum in <br />York. I <Gap><Score num="1" />had to wear</Gap> very old-fashioned, heavy dresses and <br />people <Gap><Score num="1" />could take</Gap> photos of themselves with me if they wanted.’ <I>Sally </I> <LineBreak size="13" /><br />‘I met my husband Richard in France. I was working as a waitress and he was there picking mushrooms. He <Gap><Score num="1" />didn&apos;t have to work</Gap> hard but the mushrooms were kept in the dark and they smelt terrible. By the end of the day, so did Richard! He <Gap><Score num="1" />wasn&apos;t allowed to eat</Gap> with us until he’d had a very long shower!’ <I>Carrie </I> <LineBreak size="13" /><br />‘When I was ten I acted as one of the two children in <I>Mary Poppins</I> in a London theatre. There were eight of us children altogether and we <Gap><Score num="1" />were only allowed to be</Gap> on stage twice a week. The acting was great but we <Gap><Score num="1" />weren&apos;t allowed to miss</Gap> our lessons and we <Gap><Score num="1" />had to take</Gap> exams at the end of the year.’ <I>Mark</I></Question></Content></GapFillInput><Feedback playallOn="1" showAnswersOn="1" animatedFeedbackOn="1" testModeOn="0" instantFeedbackOn="0"><Sounds /></Feedback><GenericActivity hintsNextTo="0" timerIsOn="0" CDPrefsFolder="preferences/" CDPrefsFile="cd.xml"><ActivityCanvas graphicAlpha="100" folder="" file="" colourAlpha="100" colour="transparent" /><SoundLibrary y="10" x="10" isOn="0" /><VideoLibrary h="252" w="385" y="78" x="10" isOn="0" /><Assets /></GenericActivity></Activity></Entry></CD-RAT>