<CD-RAT><Entry><HWD>REAL</HWD><Activity><EmptyActivity /><Feedback playallOn="1" showAnswersOn="1" animatedFeedbackOn="1" testModeOn="0" instantFeedbackOn="0"><Sounds /></Feedback><GenericActivity hintsNextTo="0" timerIsOn="0" CDPrefsFolder="xml/" CDPrefsFile="cd.xml"><ActivityCanvas graphicAlpha="100" folder="" file="" colourAlpha="100" colour="transparent" /><SoundLibrary y="10" x="10" isOn="0" /><VideoLibrary h="240" w="320" y="79" x="6" layer="2" isOn="1"><Item bDefault="1" endTime="135.44" startTime="0" duration="135.44" id="1" file="Int_06.flv" folder="video/" /></VideoLibrary><Assets><Asset h="410" w="340" y="70" x="330" layer="1" type="text"><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Reality TV: is there too much of it?</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Interviewer</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">Nowadays, our TV networks are dominated by so-called ‘Reality TV’ … shows where the public gets involved as famous and not-so-famous personalities find themselves doing things like trying to survive in the middle of a jungle; competing for a job with a top businessman, or starting out on the road to fame and fortune by winning a competition for wannabe pop stars … every week millions tune in to the so-called ‘reality shows’ … the TV phenomenon of the modern age.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">But are there too many of these shows? And are we getting tired of so-called ‘Reality TV’? I went out and asked some members of the public.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Aneefa</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I think what reality TV is … is where ordinary people are put into situations where they have every aspect of their life filmed and I think my biggest problem with that is the invasion of privacy, the fact that you no longer have a private life.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>David</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I think it’s just fantastic to see ordinary people on TV. Their lives are so much more interesting than celebrities. You know, it’s great hearing the opinions of people on Big Brother, knowing what they think about things and what they think about the world. I think it’s just fantastic.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Jennifer</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I don’t like reality TV shows very much. Sometimes I find myself watching them even though I don’t want to but I like reality TV shows that have a theme, like people who are all hairdressers or models or farmers or some thing that ties them all together. When it’s just ordinary people being ordinary people it’s less exciting, I think. </FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Graham</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I think reality TV is a really strange thing. I don’t like it at all and I certainly would never watch that kind of programme. I just think it’s an excuse for people to go on TV and then for everyone to talk about them rather than actually doing something with their own lives.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Sarahjane</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I don’t watch TV at all. I find it boring … not boring … it’s … I find people more interesting so I don’t watch television at all.</FONT></P></Asset></Assets></GenericActivity></Activity></Entry></CD-RAT>