<CD-RAT><Entry><HWD>REAL</HWD><Activity><EmptyActivity /><Feedback playallOn="1" showAnswersOn="1" animatedFeedbackOn="1" testModeOn="0" instantFeedbackOn="0"><Sounds /></Feedback><GenericActivity hintsNextTo="0" timerIsOn="0" CDPrefsFolder="xml/" CDPrefsFile="cd.xml"><ActivityCanvas graphicAlpha="100" folder="" file="" colourAlpha="100" colour="transparent" /><SoundLibrary y="10" x="10" isOn="0" /><VideoLibrary h="240" w="320" y="63" x="7" layer="2" isOn="1"><Item bDefault="1" endTime="200.04" startTime="0" duration="200.04" id="1" file="int_11.flv" folder="video/" /></VideoLibrary><Assets><Asset h="410" w="335" y="60" x="330" layer="1" type="text"><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Should all forms of hunting be banned? </B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Amy</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I think all forms of hunting should be banned because I’m a vegetarian and I think eating meat is completely unnecessary so I think it’s cruel, I think it’s unnecessary and I definitely think it should be banned.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Jennifer</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I think that forms of hunting should be banned. I think that most hunters are just quite cruel and that animals aren’t really given a chance to just have a nice free life. It’s not fair to them.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Sarahjane</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I don’t think all forms of hunting should be banned. I think within reason it’s not a problem.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Winek</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I’m not sure that all forms of hunting should be banned. In some cases it’s actually necessary to allow people to hunt for animals for environmental reason(s). I’m not so sure about hunting for sport or for pleasure.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Should it be made illegal for parents to smack their children?</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Caroline</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I don’t think smacking children should be made illegal. Obviously it’s difficult because parents should be able to discipline their children as they see fit, and a smack on the leg is not the same as physical abuse. But I think ultimately it’s the parents’ right to discipline and bring up their children as they see fit.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Jennifer</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">No, I don’t think that parents smacking their children should be made illegal. I don’t think that people should smack their children but making it illegal means that it would never be allowed and I think that in some cases children’s behaviour means that that’s the only thing that will get through to them so I think that in very extreme cases, it is probably acceptable.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Winek</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I have a very strong opinion about using force or smacking children and I don’t think anyone should be allowed to exercise this, anyone should be allowed to do this because it all comes back.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Should military service be compulsory for all young men and women?</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Caroline</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I’m not sure if military service should be made compulsory for all young men and women. In my father’s time he did military service and he said actually it made him a better person and developed character and gave him some skills. This day and age we have so many choices that perhaps it should be a choice rather than a compulsory decision. I don’t know. Jury’s out.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Sarahjane</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">It’s a very tough question but I don’t think that it’s unreasonable to ask all young men to do military service of six months to a year with an option to do civil service instead.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Winek</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000">I strongly disagree with the point of view that military service should be compulsory for every man and woman. People should be free and people should have the choice whether they want to join the military forces or not and if they want to be soldiers they should be paid for.</FONT></P></Asset></Assets></GenericActivity></Activity></Entry></CD-RAT>