<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<data>
<![CDATA[
<b>Test Master </b><br><br>
<p>The tests on this Test Master CD-ROM will provide you with an invaluable new resource to accompany New Cutting Edge.</p>
<br><b>Easy to use</b>
<ul>
<li>The tests are based strictly on the content of New Cutting Edge, providing a fair measure of students' progress. </li>
<li>An interactive menu makes it easy to find the tests you are looking for. </li>
<li>Keys are provided to make marking the tests as straightforward as possible. </li>
<li>The audio files for the listening tests are conveniently located on the same CD.</li>
</ul><br>
<b>Types of test</b><br>
<p>The Test Master CD contains these types of test.</p>
<b><ul>
  <li>Placement Tests</li>
<li>ModuleTests</li>
  <li>Mid-course Tests</li>
  <li>End of Level Test</li>
</ul></b><br>
<b>Flexible</b><br>
<p>You can print the tests out and use them as they are – or you can adapt them. You can use Microsoft ® Word to edit them as you wish to suit your teaching situation, your students or your syllabus. Here are some of the things you may wish to do. </p>
<ul>
  <li>Delete or add exercises to make the test shorter or longer.</li>
  <li>Delete exercises or items which relate to points which you decided to skip.</li>
  <li>Add in exercises to cover extra content you introduced into the course.</li>
  <li>Edit exercises to make them harder or easier, or to introduce key vocabulary.</li>
  <li>Edit the format of exercises so that they are consistent with other exams that you use.</li>
  <li>Personalise the content of exercises to bring them to life. For example, incorporate the names of students in the class, other teachers in the school, famous people and places from your country ...  </li>
  <li>Use the audio scripts to create extra listening exercises &ndash; for example by removing words to create gap fills, adding options to create multiple choice exercises or introducing deliberate mistakes for the students to correct.</li>
  <li>Add in the name and/or logo of your school at the head of the test.</li>
</ul>
<p>Finally, save your new version on your hard drive.</p><br>
<b>Using this CD</b><br>
<p>The ideal way to use this CD-ROM is to treat it as a master. Copy the tests to the hard drive of your computer and burn the audio files to CD or copy them on to cassette. </p>
<ul>
  <li><b>Test files</b> The installation wizard will copy the files to your hard drive. </li>
  <li><b>Audio files </b>If you don't have a CD burner or if you prefer to teach with cassettes, you can simply put the Test Master CD into the CD drive of an ordinary hi-fi and copy the audio files onto a blank cassette. </li>
</ul><br>
<br>


]]>
</data>