<CD-RAT><Entry><HWD>LF/PRES1</HWD><Activity><GapFillInput layer="1" h="460" w="670" y="10" x="10" show-wordpool="1" wordpool-position="above"><Title alignment="left" isOn="1">Prefixes and suffixes<br /></Title><Instruction alignment="left" isOn="1">Choose a prefix or suffix from the word pool to type into each of the gaps.<br /></Instruction><ReferenceObject soundIsOn="0" videoIsOn="0" defaultHeight="245" alignment="left" isOn="1"><Asset file="06042301.jpg" folder="images/" h="228" w="275" y="2" x="198" layer="1" type="graphic" /></ReferenceObject><ScrollableAssets /><Content><Question>More and more people nowadays are feeling <Gap><Score num="1" />over</Gap>worked and in need of something to help them with their <Gap><Score num="1" />over</Gap>active lives. Take Jamie for example, a success<Gap><Score num="1" />ful</Gap> barrister, who just needed to chill out. He knew he had become <Gap><Score num="1" />mono</Gap>syllabic with his family and less respons<Gap><Score num="1" />ive</Gap> to everyone in general. He felt his life was <Gap><Score num="1" />in</Gap>complete. He sought some advice on complementary therapies from his friends, and received <br />some impress<Gap><Score num="1" />ive</Gap> feedback from them on therapies such as hypnotherapy and aromatherapy. The treatments certainly didn’t appear too price<Gap><Score num="1" />y</Gap>, and after a couple of sessions of both therapies, he felt more cheer<Gap><Score num="1" />ful</Gap> and humor<Gap><Score num="1" />ous</Gap> about life in general. Trivial things that formerly caused him to worry became<br /><Gap><Score num="1" />un</Gap>important, and he even looked forward to the often dull <Gap><Score num="1" />bi</Gap>annual work conference! He now has a more harmoni<Gap><Score num="1" />ous</Gap> family life, and has just redecorated a room in his house lovely atmospher<Gap><Score num="1" />ic</Gap> colours where the whole family can go to relax and recuperate. </Question></Content></GapFillInput><Feedback playallOn="1" showAnswersOn="1" animatedFeedbackOn="1" testModeOn="0" instantFeedbackOn="0"><Sounds /></Feedback><GenericActivity hintsNextTo="0" timerIsOn="0" CDPrefsFolder="xml/" CDPrefsFile="cd.xml"><ActivityCanvas graphicAlpha="100" folder="" file="" colourAlpha="100" colour="transparent" /><SoundLibrary y="10" x="10" isOn="0" /><VideoLibrary h="264.95" w="385" y="75.05" x="10" isOn="0" /><Assets /></GenericActivity></Activity></Entry></CD-RAT>