<CD-RAT><Entry><HWD>REAL</HWD><Activity><EmptyActivity /><Feedback playallOn="1" showAnswersOn="1" animatedFeedbackOn="1" testModeOn="0" instantFeedbackOn="0"><Sounds /></Feedback><GenericActivity hintsNextTo="0" timerIsOn="0" CDPrefsFolder="xml/" CDPrefsFile="cd.xml"><ActivityCanvas graphicAlpha="100" folder="" file="" colourAlpha="100" colour="transparent" /><SoundLibrary y="10" x="10" isOn="0" /><VideoLibrary h="240" w="320" y="75.6" x="8" layer="1" isOn="1"><Item bDefault="1" endTime="196.56" startTime="0" duration="196.56" id="1" file="Elementary03CD.flv" folder="video/" /></VideoLibrary><Assets><Asset h="440.95" w="330" y="7" x="335" layer="2" type="text"><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>When do people in your country usually eat?</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Amy:</B> In New Zealand most people have breakfast at around seven or eight o’clock in the morning. Then lunchtime is between twelve and one. Most people would have dinner between about six and seven p.m.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Jennifer:</B> In Pennsylvania people eat breakfast usually between seven and nine a.m. and lunchtime is usually between eleven and one o&apos;clock. And finally, supper is usually when people get home from work, maybe between five o&apos;clock and seven o&apos;clock.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Caroline:</B> I&apos;m from Norfolk in England, I don&apos;t know about people in general, but in my house I have breakfast very early. I have two young sons and they get up about six, six-thirty so we have an early breakfast. We have dinner in our house quite late maybe eight o’clock at night or nine o&apos;clock. Erm, lunch I usually have, if I remember, between one and two.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Alissa: </B>I&apos;m from Colombia. In Cali, we usually have breakfast at six-thirty, lunch at twelve and dinner at seven.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Tessie</B>: In Greece, people have a small breakfast in the morning, and lunch at about two o&apos;clock in the afternoon and a late dinner at about nine o&apos;clock.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>When do shops open and close in your country?</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Amy:</B> In New Zealand most shops open at nine o’clock in the morning and close at five o’clock at night, that’s for both the weekdays and the weekends. But on Thursday nights we have a late night where shops close at nine o’clock at night.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Kate:</B> In England some shops are open 24hrs a day, except on Sundays, when they are open from around ten until four in the afternoon. Most shops are open on Mondays to Fridays between nine and five o’clock in the afternoon.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>David:</B> I lived in Italy and shops in Italy, open early about eight-thirty, nine o’clock, but then they close in the afternoon. They close for lunch between one o’clock and three o’clock and they open again in the evening and close quite late about 8 o clock. But on Sunday the shops are closed all day - most of them.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Tessie:</B> Erm, most shops in Greece open at nine o’clock in the morning. They close at two o’clock in the afternoon, and they open again at five o clock in the evening until eight o’clock in the evening.</FONT></P></Asset></Assets></GenericActivity></Activity></Entry></CD-RAT>