<CD-RAT><Entry><HWD>REAL</HWD><Activity><EmptyActivity /><Feedback playallOn="1" showAnswersOn="1" animatedFeedbackOn="1" testModeOn="0" instantFeedbackOn="0"><Sounds /></Feedback><GenericActivity hintsNextTo="0" timerIsOn="0" CDPrefsFolder="xml/" CDPrefsFile="cd.xml"><ActivityCanvas graphicAlpha="100" folder="" file="" colourAlpha="100" colour="transparent" /><SoundLibrary y="10" x="10" isOn="0" /><VideoLibrary h="240" w="320" y="63" x="5" layer="2" isOn="1"><Item bDefault="1" endTime="165.88" startTime="0" duration="165.88" id="1" file="PreInt15.flv" folder="video/" /></VideoLibrary><Assets><Asset h="410" w="342" y="60" x="327" layer="1" type="text"><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>What would you do if you were very rich? </B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Aneefa:</B> If I were extremely rich, I think I would go travelling. I would travel to lots of different countries because I would be able to afford to stay there for quite a long time and experience different cultures.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>David:</B> If I was very rich, I wouldn’t work. Well I wouldn’t work for money obviously but I would work for charity. I’d like to do some work for global children’s charities. I think if I was rich, that’s what I would do with my time.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Jennifer:</B> If I was very rich, I would host a huge party in a mansion and I would invite friends of mine who I haven’t seen in ten or twenty years to come to this mansion and dress up in fancy costumes and have beautiful food and music and just so all of my friends would be together in one place.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Winek:</B> If I were very rich, I would like to share my wealth with other people. I would like to be able to give money to charity but I would also like to save some of that and keep myself and my family entertained as well.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>If your house was on fire, what would you save?</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Caroline</B>: If my house was on fire, I would save my children first and then their favourite toys because my life isn’t worth living without them.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Graham:</B> If my house was on fire, I suppose I’d save the photographs I have. I think they’re really important memories.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Jennifer:</B> If my house was on fire, I would save two things. I would save my cat and I would save a folder full of important insurance papers.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Sarah:</B> If my house was on fire, I think the first thing that I would save is obviously my family and then photos because you can’t replace those.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>If you could be another person for a day, who would it be?</B></FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Caroline</B>: If I could be someone else for a day, I think I’d like to be a man so I could experience life from a male point of view.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Graham:</B> If I could be another person for one day, I think I’d be Prime Minister because I think there’s a lot of things that need to be changed in this country.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Jennifer:</B> If I could be another person for a day, I would be the young Audrey Hepburn because I know that my boyfriend thinks that she’s beautiful.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000" /></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Tessie:</B> If I could be another person, I would choose to be an astronaut because I would be able to travel to space. </FONT></P></Asset></Assets></GenericActivity></Activity></Entry></CD-RAT>