<CD-RAT><Entry><HWD>REAL</HWD><Activity><EmptyActivity /><Feedback playallOn="1" showAnswersOn="1" animatedFeedbackOn="1" testModeOn="0" instantFeedbackOn="0"><Sounds /></Feedback><GenericActivity hintsNextTo="0" timerIsOn="0" CDPrefsFolder="xml/" CDPrefsFile="cd.xml"><ActivityCanvas graphicAlpha="100" folder="" file="" colourAlpha="100" colour="transparent" /><SoundLibrary y="10" x="10" isOn="0" /><VideoLibrary h="240" w="320" y="63" x="8" layer="2" isOn="1"><Item bDefault="1" endTime="81.31" startTime="0" duration="81.31" id="2" file="PreInt11.flv" folder="video/" /></VideoLibrary><Assets><Asset h="410" w="345" y="60" x="335" layer="1" type="text"><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Jennifer</B>: My favourite hobby is making ceramic pots on a potter’s wheel and I like it because it is very creative. It is also something that doesn’t require a lot of thought so I can turn my brain off for a while. </FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Winek</B>: My hobby is collecting CDs. I think I’ve got a couple of hundred of them at home with different types of music, ranging from classical music through jazz, pop, to hip hop.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Sarah</B>: My favourite hobby is spending time in my garden. I like looking after my vegetables and my chickens.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Amy:</B> My father has always played the guitar and when I was about oh maybe about eighteen or nineteen, he gave me a guitar and he started to teach me how to play it. And it didn’t take long before I was playing songs by myself and making up songs with friends and just really enjoying it. I really enjoy playing ballads and the blues on the guitar, but really anything I can sing along to, I really enjoy.</FONT></P><P ALIGN="LEFT"><FONT FACE="Stone Informal" SIZE="13" COLOR="#000000"><B>Graham</B>: I’m really interested in sports. I do a lot of different sports. I’m keen on running and I also play football. I also like to go to the gym.</FONT></P></Asset></Assets></GenericActivity></Activity></Entry></CD-RAT>